<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://m4gg13.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>23 November 2023</title>
      <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/particle-sandbox/23november2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://m4gg13.github.io/particle-sandbox/23november2023/</guid>
      <description>ive got some education on the subject and a liiittle experience with qiskit
wanted to know what kinds of algorithms get used in particle simulations. that&amp;rsquo;s just chemical simulations reallly. so i turned to this article and discovered that of the suggested algorithms that are available in the qiskit library, we&amp;rsquo;ve got Trotterization. Suzuki Trotter specifically. So I guess that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;re going with.
Also, got this repo where someone started doing the work of setting up standard model visualization things so i&amp;rsquo;ll fork that and add python to it for qiskit</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25 November 2023</title>
      <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/github-pages-hugo/25november2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://m4gg13.github.io/github-pages-hugo/25november2023/</guid>
      <description>was a struggle but used these resources
one two and figured out a structure like this (screenshot of and link to private repo) (screenshot of and link to public repo) note: the repos&amp;rsquo; structures might have changed since this post was made. Refer to the screenshots if so
and determined that for setup you&amp;rsquo;re going to want to follow these steps. details further down the page
install dependencies (links?) make a github pages repo (link) (also stuff about watching it build and deploy) hugo new site or whatever run hugo to generate the public/ folder where your compiled code is.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://m4gg13.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m learning Hugo, one step at a time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Feed</title>
      <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://m4gg13.github.io/posts/</guid>
      <description>this is where the links to all my posts go</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Making a Github pages site with Hugo</title>
      <link>https://m4gg13.github.io/posts/firstpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://m4gg13.github.io/posts/firstpost/</guid>
      <description>It was a bit of a pain in the butt!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
